Hurry up!
เร็วเข้า
I'm starving.
หิวจะเเย่เเล้ว
Hurry up, quickly!
รีบตื่นเร็ว
No more sleep!
เลิกนอนได้เเล้ว
Sorry.
ขอโทษ ขอโทษ
Hurry up and get breakfast.
ต้องรีบๆปเตรียมอาหารเช้าเเล้ว
It's already noon.
ตอนนี้ก็เที่ยงแล้ว
I have helped you to prepare XERO battle suit for you.
ดีนะที่ฉันช่วยคุณออกแบบชุดHXERO
But you treat me like this.
เเต่คุณดันแบบนี้กับฉัน
I'm really sorry.
ฉันขอโทษจริงๆ
I really expect the reaction from Retto after he came back.
เดี๋ยวรอกลับมากันฉันจะคอยดูปฏิกิริยาของเร็ตโตะ
Stop talking. I would like to eat.
อย่าเพิ่งพูดถึง ฉันจะกินข้าว
SUPER HXEROS
ซุปเปอร์HXEROS
Episode 10 "Two Kiraras"
ตอนที่ 10 "คิราระสองคน"
Then, let's go, guys.
งั้นพวกเราไปกันเถอะ ทุกคน
Since being a hero,
ตั้งแต่เป็นฮีโร่
when in Tokyo, you really need to visit this street.
มาถึงโตเกียวเเล้วต้องมาเดินถนนเส้นนี้ให้ได้
I feel the same.
ฉันก็คิดเหมือนกัน
I think Ginkgo seems to be in high mood.
ฉันเห็นกินโกโยนะดูตื่นเต้นมาก
Is she familiar with Akihabara?
เธอสนิทกับอากิฮาบาระเหรอ
It seems to be.
น่าจะใช่
Let's go.
พวกเราไปกันเถอะ
Where shall we go first？
จะไปที่ไหนก่อนดี
Wait a moment.
รอแป๊ปนะ
Although We're here for sightseeing
ถึงแม้ว่าฉันจะมาที่นี่เพื่อเที่ยว
if so many of us hangs around.
แต่เรามีคนเยอะมาก ถ้าเดินไปเดินมา
It's not only inconvenient, but also is a shame, isn't it?
ไม่ใช่แค่เกะกะ เเต่มันยังดูน่าอายด้วยใช่มั้ย
So shall we split into two groups?
เราควรแบ่งไปเป็นสองกลุ่มมั้ย
It's reasonable.
มีเหตุผล
Let's make it four and five.
ง้ันก็เเบ่งกลุ่มนึง5คนกลุ่มนึง4คนละกัน
In this case,
ถ้างั้น
let the person with high H value
ให้คนที่มีพลัง H สูงตามลำดับ
to choose which group they like to join.
วิธีการเลือกกลุ่มที่ตนเองชอบ เป็นไง
Rejecting!
ปฏิเสธ
I don't want to say such a shameful thing,
เรื่องน่าอายเเบบนี้ฉันไม่อยากเลือกหรอก
I'm also embarrassed.
ฉันก็รู้สึกเขินเหมือนกัน
Decide with rock and paper (play finger guesing if no scissors)
ถ้างั้นตัดสินใจด้วยการเป่ายิงฉุบ(ไม่ต้องออกกรรไกร)
Group with it!
ออกค้อนเเละกระดาษมาเเบ่งกลุ่มละกัน
So,
แล้ว
let's show the three people around.
ให้เราพาสามคนนี้ไปเยี่ยมชม
See you later!
งั้นเดี๋ยวมาเจอกัน
Then leave these two to us!
งั้นสองคนนี้ปล่อยให้เป็นหน้าของฉันเอง
Why is Moeno as the captain?
ทำไมหัวทีมต้องเป็นโมยะชิด้วยล่ะ
Because of you,
เป็นเพราะคุณ
I'm in a different group with Enjo.
ทำให้ฉันและเยนโจอยู่คนละทีม
You're annoying!
คุณน่ารำคาญจัง
It's all your fault to propose group action.
ต้องโทษคุณที่คุณคิดเกมบ้าๆนี่
See!
ดูสิ
You don't think it's a big loss in your own mind.
คุณไม่ได้รู้สึกว่ามันเป็นความผิดพลาดของตัวเองเหรอ
I don't know what you are talking about.
ฉันไม่รู้ว่าคุณกำลังพูดถึงอะไร
When did the two become so close?
สองคนนั้นสนิทกันเเบบนี้ตั้งเเต่เมื่อไหร่
Thanks to this, finally we can together to have a good chat, Bai.
ไม่ได้เห็นเเบบนี้มานานเเล้ว สองคนได้คุยกันดีเเล้ว อาชิโระ
I don't feel so happy.
ฉันรู้สึกไม่ค่อยดีใจมากเท่าไหร่
So where shall we go now?
ตอนนี้เราจะไปที่ไหนกัน
A place where you will be happy, Bai.
อาชิโระพวกคุณต้องดีใจเเน่ๆ
Then I'll look forward to it.
ฉันจะคอยดู
I'm wondering where the other group is going.
สงสัยจังอีกกลุ่มจะไปไหนกันนะ
Me too!
ใช่อ่ะสิ
So cute!
น่า...น่ารักจัง
I don't expect to be able to
ฉันไม่คิดเลยว่าจะได้อยู่ในโตเกียว
interact with real owls so close in Tokyo.
โต้ตอบกับนกฮูกตัวจริงอย่างใกล้ชิด
While cat cafes and maid tea shops are fine.
คาเฟ่แมวเเละคนทำความสะอาดร้านก็ดีเหมือนกันนะ
The shop few aficionados know.
แต่ร้านแบบนี้มีอยู่ไม่กี่คนเท่านั้นที่รู้จัก
It's also a reminder of this street.
ยังเป็นกลิ่นของถนนสายนี้อีกด้วยนะ
Anyway,
พูดถึงเเล้ว
Owls also have all kinds of expressions,
เพิ่งรู้ว่านกฮูกมีหลากหลายอารมณ์อีกด้วย
and their sounds are so quiet. I feel so healing.
และเสียงร้องที่เงียบสงบของมันให้ความรู้สึกผ่อนคลายมาก
Let's see.
ทุกคนมาดูสิ
This owl looks like Master.
นกฮูกตัวนี้ดูเหมือนครูเลย
Is that so?
จริงเหรอ
The one next looks like Hoshino!
ตัวข้างๆให้ความรู้สึกคล้ายกับโฮชิโนะมาก
Show it to Hoshino when we get back.
กลับไปให้โฮชิโนะดูสิ
You two are very close!
พวกคุณสนิทกันมาก
Enjo and Hoshino
เอนโจและโฮชิโนะ
are not really so close.
ไม่ได้สนิทกันขนาดนั้นหรอก
I mean those kids.
ฉันหมายถึงเด็ก ๆ พวกนี้
That's it.
อ่อ
If I heard you correctly.
ถ้าฉันได้ยินไม่ผิด
I came with you when you said you were going to hero's shop.
ฉันได้ยินคุณพูดว่าพวกคุณจะไปที่ร้านฮีโร่ถึงมาด้วยไง
Where does the H go?
ฉันบอกว่า "H"อันนั้นหายไปไหน
And those underage can't come to this kind of shops.
อีกอย่างผู้เยาว์ไม่สามารถเข้าชมร้านพวกนี้ได้ใช่มั้ย
Don't worry Kirara !
ไม่ต้องกังวลนะ คูโมะ
The first floor only sells some trick toys.
ชั้นหนึ่งมีเเต่ของเล่นหุ่นยนต์
It's on the second floor selling adult goods!
สินค้าสำหรับผู้ใหญ่มีจำหน่ายที่ชั้นสองเท่านั้น
That is to say!
นั่นน่ะสิ
Le me ask whether Kirara get one too
ฉันคิดว่าคิราระควรซื้อด้วย
Just in case.
ใช้ตอนจำเป็น
Don't ne so close to me with that!
อย่าเอาของแบบนั้นมาใกล้ฉัน
I'm gonna go out and have some fresh air.
ฉันจะออกไปสูดอากาศสักแปป
She runs away.
เธอหนีไปเเล้ว
So embarrassed.
อายจังเลย
What's up?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น
Cong Yu, what are you doing?
มุราซาเมะ คุณกำลังทำอะไรน่ะ
He is so pure.
ไร้เดียงสาจริงๆ
Thank you for being HXEROS.
เพราะคุณฉันถึงมีวิธีที่จะเป็น HXEROSได้
I've been watching your interaction.
ฉันเพิ่งสังเกตการกระทำของพวกคุณสองคน
Relationship between you and Enjo Retto do not seem to have changed?
ความสัมพันธ์ของคุณกับเอนโจเร็ตโตะดูเหมือนจะไม่เปลี่ยนเลย
So what if it is.
ใช่แล้วไงต่อ
Sure enough.
นั่นไง
I have made up my mind, Hoshino Kirara.
ฉันได้ตัดสินใจแล้ว โฮชิโนะคิราระ
This time I will definitely capture Enjo Retto's heart.
คราวนี้ฉันจะคว้าหัวใจของเอนโจเร็ตโตะให้ได้แน่นอน
Then I have something to do next,
แล้วฉันมีเรื่องต้องทำต่อ
So, I'm going back first.
งั้นฉันกลับก่อนนะ
And don't be too careless!
ฉันขอแนะนำว่าคุณอย่าประมาทเกินไป
Except us,
ยกเว้นเรา
maybe someone else is also interested in the guy.
อาจจะมีคนอื่นสนใจผู้ชายคนนั้นด้วย
Am I in a crisis now?
เป็นไปได้มั้ยว่าตอนนี้ฉันอยู่ในช่วงวิกฤต
Where are you? Sora
คุณอยู่ที่ไหนโซระ
Maihima, this way.
ฮิเมเมะ ทางนี้
There is such a place like this in Akihabara!
ยังมีสถานที่เเบบนี้ในอากิฮาบาระอีกเหรอ
I'm here for the first time too.
นี่เป็นครั้งเเรกของฉันที่มาที่นี่
This is interesting.
รู้สึกน่าสนใจมาก
It's "VR heroine"!
“ นางเอก VR”
Are you interested in it?
คุณสนใจเรื่องนี้พวกนี้ด้วยเหรอ
It's Ginkgo.
มันเป็นของกินโกโยนะ
The VR game is set to ask a childhood friend who lives next door to teach him to read.
การตั้งเเค่เกม VR นี้ ขณะที่เล่นกับเด็กของคุณโปรดสอนให้ตัวเองอ่านด้วย
A childhood friend
เล่นกับเด็ก
The game is very realistic.
เกมนี้มีความสมจริงมาก
It's a rare chance, just play around!
โอกาสนีเหายาก คุณก็เล่นไปเถอะ
Then, I'll try.
งั้น ฉันจะลองดู
What do you see Enjo?
เอนโจ คุณเห็นอะไรมั้ย
Classroom... and the girl just now.
ห้องเรียน ... และเด็กผู้หญิงเมื่อกี้
There seems to be no problem
ดูเหมือนจะไม่มีปัญหา
In fact,
จริงๆแล้วเกมนี้
the study of the game is only the appearance
ส่วนของการเรียนเป็นเพียงการแสดงเท่านั้น
and the focus is on being able to kiss girls.
หลักๆคือสามารถผูกมิตรกับสาว ๆ
He's not just content with VR.
เขาคงจะไม่พึงพอใจกับ VR หรอก
In recent VR games,
เกม VR ล่าสุด
is even the touch feeling so realistic?
การสัมผัสยังเหมือนจริงมาก
It is as if someone is actually just there.
เหมือนมีคนอยู่ที่นั่น
Wait... Enjo
รอก่อน ... เอนโจ
What shall I do?
ทำยังไง
If it does turn out that way.
ถ้ามันเป็นอย่างงั้นจริงๆ
It's amazing!
เจ๋งมาก
As if a girl is really there in front of my eyes.
ราวกับว่ามีหญิงสาวอยู่ตรงหน้าคุณจริงๆ
What the hell am I doing?
ฉันกำลังทำอะไรเนี่ย
I'm just like a freak!
ฉันนี่มันลามกชัดๆ
The feeling is good!
รู้สึกดีจริงๆ
Exactly.
ใช่
That's where my H energy comes from.
นี่คือแหล่งที่มาของพลัง H ของฉัน
I'm a top student at school or at home.
ไม่ว่าจะเป็นในโรงเรียนหรือที่บ้านก็ได้เกียรตินิยมทั้งนั้น
When I'm tired of this life,
ตอนที่ฉันรู้สึกเบื่อๆ
I was invited to join HXEROS.
ฉันได้รับเชิญให้เข้าร่วม HXEROS
But,
แต่
because other players are all that virtue,
ด้วยบุคลิกของคนในสมาชิก
I'm always busy managing them in the end.
ฉันมักจะยุ่งอยู่กับการจัดการพวกมัน
And my source of H energy is...
และแหล่งที่มาของพลัง H ของฉันคือ ...
"Moral violation"
“ การมีคุณธรรม”
There seemed to be a strange sound just now.
เมื่อกี้ดูเหมือนจะมีเสียงแปลก ๆ
What's up?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น
Ginkgo,
กินโกโยนะ
there's a reason for that.
คือว่า ... มันมีเหตุผลของมันนะ
Please don't tell others about what just happened.
อย่าบอกคนอื่นว่าเรื่องที่เกิดเมื่อกี้
Please!
ถือว่าฉันขอร้องล่ะ
Please! ?
นี่มันเหมือนขอร้องยังไง!?
Um...
คือว่า
I already have someone else I like,
เพราะฉันมีคนที่ฉันชอบอยู่แล้ว
so please don't do it even as a joke.
ถึงแม้จะเป็นเรื่องล้อเล่นเเต่คุณโปรดอย่าทำเเบบนี้
Do you misunderstand Enjo.
คุณเข้าใจผิดเเล้ว เยนโจ
I don't have such feelings for you.
ฉันไม่ได้จะใช้ความรู้สึกเเบบนั้นกับคุณ ...
Is this to say
หรือว่า
Wouldn't the members of the Saitama branch do such a thing?
สมาชิกในกลุ่มไซตามะจะไม่ทำเรื่องเเบบนี้เหรอ
Clearly.
เรื่องนี้ต้องบอกด้วยเหรอ
I was cheated.
ฉันโดนหลอกเเล้ว
Cong Yu told me other branches relied on this to store H energy.
มุราซาเมะเคยบอกฉันว่ากลุ่มอื่นใช้สิ่งนี้ในการสะสมพลัง H
It's impossible.
เเค่คิดก็รู้ว่าเป็นไปไม่ได้
Really sorry!
ขอโทษจริงๆ
I didn't mean that,
ฉันไม่ได้หมายถึงอย่างนั้นจริงๆ
I probably knew the whole story.
ฉันพอจะรู้เรื่องราวทั้งหมดเเเล้ว
But
แต่
Saitama branch is really amazing.
กลุ่มไซตามะน่าทึ่งจริงๆ
what shall I say, is it serious or pure?
ฉันควรจะจริงจังหรือจริงใจเหรอ
Even if you don't do that.
แม้ว่าคุณจะไม่ทำเช่นนั้นก็ตาม
It's also top-level in terms of Kisei Chuu.
ในแง่ของการกำจัดคิเซย์จู จะต้องมีระดับความเเข็งเเกร่งที่สูงมากเลยทีเดียว
In normal person's eyes,
ในสายตาของคนปกติ
Our Tokyo branch shall feel strange.
ที่แปลกน่าจะเป็นกลุ่มโตเกียวของเรา
I don't feel that way.
เเต่ฉันไม่คิดว่ามันเป็นเรื่องแปลก
No hero cares what others think when he fights.
ไม่มีฮีโร่คนไหนสนใจสายตาผู้อื่นในระหว่างการต่อสู้หรอก
Thank you!
ขอบคุณ
Hearing you say that,
พอได้ยินคุณพูดอย่างนั้น
I don't feel so embarrassed anymore.
ฉันไม่รู้สึกอายอีกต่อไปแล้ว
I really admire the girl you like.
ฉันอิจฉาผู้หญิงที่คุณชอบจริงๆ
So,
แล้ว
thank you so much today.
วันนี้ขอบคุณมาก
It's me that need to say thank you!
ฉันต้องขอบคุณพวกคุณสิ
Sorry!
ขอโทษ
I'm gonna go to the bathroom, you guys go first.
ฉันจะไปห้องน้ำ พวกคุณไปก่อนเลย
I see.
ฉันรู้เเล้ว
If we get separated, we'll go first.
ย้ายตัวกันเเล้วพวกเราจะไปก่อนนะ
What is she talking about?
เธอกำลังพูดถึงอะไร
How could it be so simple...
มันจะง่ายขนาดนี้ได้ยังไง ...
Oh, no. I'm lost.
เเย่เเล้ว ฉันหลงทาง
Now I have no rights to laugh at the Orange Horse.
ตอนนี้ฉันไม่มีสิทธิมาหัวเราะเยาะได้
Enjo,
เยนโจ
where are Taoyuan and others?
โมโมโซโนะ คนอื่น ๆ ล่ะ
I get separated from them because of the crowd.
คนเยอะไปหน่อยฉันจึงแยกตัวออกมากับพวกเขา
So you're just like me?
คุณก็เหมือนกับฉันนี่หน่า
Shall we go back together?
กลับไปด้วยกันมั้ย
Shoot with great accuracy.
ยิงเเม่นมาก
I really admire the girl you like.
ฉันอิจฉาผู้หญิงที่คุณชอบจริงๆ
This time I definitely to capture Enjo Retto's heart!
คราวนี้ฉันจะคว้าหัวใจของเอนโจเร็ตโตะให้ได้แน่นอน
We need to get something to talk...
ต้องหาเรื่องคุยซะหน่อย ...
Right.
เออใช่
We went to the Owl Cafe today,
วันนี้เราไปคาเฟ่นกฮูกด้วยเเหละ
and saw an owl looking like Hoshino.
ฉันเห็นนกฮูกที่มีลักษณะคล้ายกับโฮชิโนะเลย
I have pictures, do you want to have a sight?
ฉันถ่ายรูปมาด้วย อยากดูมั้ย
It's cute.
น่ารักจัง
But I like the one next.
เเต่ฉันชอบตัวข้างๆมากกว่า
I always feel this one just like someone else.
ฉันว่าจัวนี้ดูเหมือนใครบางคนเลย
Right,
เออใช่
where did you go today, Hoshino?
โฮชิโนะวันนี้พวกคุณไปไหนมา
Me?
ฉันเหรอ
Actually didn't go to any interesting places.
จริงๆแล้วไม่ได้ไปที่พิเศษๆเลย
Though you said that, you still bought something.
ถึงแม้ว่าคุณจะพูดอย่างนั้น แต่คุณก็ยังมีซื้อของมาอยู่
This is something had been forgotten by the Tokyo branch.
นี่คือสิ่งที่คนในกลุ่มโตเกียวลืมเอาไป
The train is about to depart.
รถไฟขบวนนี้กำลังจะออกเดินทาง
Passengers, please wait for a moment.
ผู้โดยสารกรุณารอสักครู่
Okay, we need to change here.
เอาล่ะ เราต้องเปลี่ยนรถที่นี่
Sorry,
ขอโทษ
we need to get off.
เราจะลง
It was dangerous just now.
เมื่อกี้มันอันตรายมาก
Fortunately you noticed.
โชคดีที่คุณสังเกตเห็น
Why is your hairpin missing, Hoshino?
โฮชิโนะ กิ๊บบนหัวคุณหายไปไหนเเล้ว
Did it fall when you hit someone just now?
หายไปตั้งเเต่เมื่อกี้ที่ชนคนเเล้ว
But what can I do?
แต่จะทำยังไงได้ล่ะ
I'll ask the station staff to look for it at the terminal.
ฉันจะไปขอให้เจ้าหน้าที่ช่วยหา
Don't need to do this.
ไม่จำเป็นต้องทำถึงขนาดนี้หรอก
Anyway, just buy another one.
ยังไงก็ค่อยไปซื้อเถอะ
When did I start wearing that hairpin.
ฉันเริ่มติดกิ็บอันนั้นตั้งเเต่เมื่อไหร่
Obviously wear it every day.
เห็นๆอยู่ว่าติดทุกวัน
I can't remember.
ฉันจำไม่ได้
It feels like that the hairpin is a very important thing.
ฉันรู้สึกว่ากิ๊บเป็นสิ่งที่สำคัญมาก
Finally found it.
ในที่สุดก็เจอเเล้ว
Thank you very much.
ขอบคุณมาก
It's great to have found it!
ดีใจจังที่เจอ
If it's a present from boyfriend,
ถ้าเป็นของขวัญจากแฟน
that will be terrible.
งั้นคงแย่มาก
This is not the case.
ไม่ใช่อย่างงั้น
Sorry for saying such strange words.
ขอโทษที่พูดอะไรแปลก ๆไป
It's late.
นี่ก็สายแล้ว
Do you want to contact your parents first?
คุณอยากโทรหาพ่อคุณก่อนมั้ย
No, it's okay.
ไม่ ไม่เป็นไร
Like this time,
เหมือนครั้งนี้
as a man, you need to know how to guide each other.
เป็นผู้ชายที่ต้องรู้จักเป็นผู้นำนะ
Next
ต่อไป
The final train has passed.
รถไฟขบวนสุดท้ายผ่านไปแล้ว
I think it's better to contact Uncle and ask him to pick us up.
ฉันคิดว่าฉันสามารถติดต่อคุณลุง และขอให้เขามารับเราได้
That's right.
จริงด้วย
Um, Enjo.
นั่น ใช่เยนโจรึเปล่า
What do you know about my hairpin/.
คุณรู้อะไรเกี่ยวกับกิ๊บของฉัน
I have a vague memory of when I was attacked by Kisei Chuu.
ฉันจำเวลาที่ฉันถูกคิเซย์จูโจมตีไม่ค่อยได้เลย
I can't remember when I wore it.
ฉันจำไม่ได้ว่ามันเริ่มเมื่อไหร่
If you hide something from me, please tell me!
ถ้ามีอะไรปิดบัง โปรดรีบบอกฉัน
It's not a big deal.
มันไม่ใช่เรื่องใหญ่อะไรหรอก
And since you don't remember.
อีกอย่างถึงเเม้คุณจะจำไม่ได้
Maybe it's a memory you don't like to recall!
บางทีมันอาจจะเป็นความทรงจำที่คุณไม่อยากจำก็ได้
I think,
ฉันว่า
just ask Black Kirara and she'll probably know.
แค่ถามไบโอไทท์เธอน่าจะรู้เเหละ
But why?
แต่ทำไม
I feel it is not a good idea.
ทำแบบนี้รู้สึกไม่โอเค
So,
ดังนั้น
please, tell me!
ขอร้องล่ะ โปรดบอกฉัน
I know.
ฉันรู้เเล้ว
But don't tell anyone,
ฉันไม่อย่าบอกคนอื่นหรอก
especially Taoyuan.
โดยเฉพาะโมโมโซโนะ
It's embarrassing to mention this now.
ตอนนี้ฉันรู้สึกอายที่จะพูดถึงเรื่องนี้
I actually gave you that hairpin.
กิ๊บนั้นฉันเป็นคนให้
You're a liar.
โกหก
But what does this have something to do with Kisei Chuu?
เเล้วมันเกี่ยวข้องกับคิเซย์จูยังไง
I'm afraid.
ฉันคิดว่าอาจจะเป็น
It was the marriage proposal promise that I gave you.
เพราะตอนนั้นฉันอยากจะขอแต่งงานคุณ
Morning Retto!
สวัสดีตอนเช้า โรคัตสึ
Morning Hoshino!
สวัสดีตอนเช้า โฮชิโนะ
It was hot last night!
เมื่อคืนร้อนมาก
See,
คุณดูสิ
I wore thin clothes when I slept, and even this place was bitten by mosquitoes.
ตอนนอนฉันใส่เสื้อบาง ๆ เเม้เเต่ตรงนี้ยังโดนยุงกัด
Fool!
คนโง่
Don't expose that on the way to school.
อย่าเปิดตรงนั้นระหว่างทางไปโรงเรียนสิ
Didn't I show it to you on the way to school?
ไม่ใช่ระหว่างทางไปโรงเรียนถึงจะเปิดให้ดูได้เหรอ
It's so noisy.
หนวกหูจัง
Where do you think was bitten?
คุณคิดว่าถูกกัดตรงไหน
Do not know!
ไม่รู้
I can't stand this guy!
ทนไม่ไหวกับยัยนี่เเล้วนะ
He always like to play tricks on others,
ชอบแกล้งคนอื่นแบบนี้อยู่เสมอ
and he is headstrong and arrogant.
อีกอย่างเป็นคนเอาแต่ใจและหยิ่งผยอง
But I still like this Hoshino.
แต่ฉันก็ยังชอบโฮชิโนะคนนี้
Today is his birthday,
วันนี้เป็นวันเกิดของยัยคนนี้
I need to master dominance this time.
ฉันต้องรับหน้าที่เป็นผู้นำในครั้งนี้
Bye!
ลาก่อน
What's the matter, Retto?
โรคัตสึ เป็นอะไรรึเปล่า
You call me to this place.
ยังอุส่าห์เรียกฉันมาที่นี่
And the letter is...
จดหมายฉบับนี้คือ ...
I want to propose to you. I'll wait for you at the back of the gym after school.
ฉันอยากจะขอคุณเเจ่งงาน ฉันจะรอคุณอยู่ที่หลังโรงยิมหลังเลิกเรียน
Are you serious?
จดหมายฉบับนี้คุณจริงจังใช่มั้ย
Yes!
ใช่
The plan is very smooth.
แผนไปได้ด้วยดี
Although at first glance, it says "marriage" above,
แม้ว่าแวบแรกจะบอกว่า "แต่งงาน"
but it's actually wrote "Duel".
แต่จริงๆผมเขียนไปว่า "Duel"
That's how you look at me!
คุณมองฉันด้วยสายตาแบบนี้
I wrote "duel" above.
ฉันเขียนคำว่า "Duel" ไว้อย่างชัดเจน
Do you have any misunderstanding?
คุณเข้าใจอะไรผิดรึเปล่า
No!
ไม่เอา!
Then I turned and made fun of Hoshino, he mistakes the word for marriage.
จากนั้นฉันก็หันกลับมาขำ เขียนผิดเป็นงานเเต่งงานของโฮชิโนะ
It's a perfect operation.
มันเป็นการต่อสู้ที่สมบูรณ์แบบมาก
Come on!
มาเลย
Make fun of me as usual, Hoshino.
เล่นกลกับฉันเหมือนเคย โฮชิโนะ
Since Retto said so.
ตั้งแต่โรคัตสึพูดแบบนั้น
Nothing but,
แค่
I think the marriage contract may be a little too early for our age.
ฉันคิดว่าการแต่งงานอาจจะเร็วเกินไปสำหรับอายุของเรา
So...
เช่นนั้น…
It's strange, what's going on in such atmosphere?
แปลกจัง เกิดอะไรขึ้นกับบรรยากาศเเบบนี้
It's different from what I thought.
ทำไมมันไม่เหมือนกับที่ฉันคิด
But according to her personality,
แต่ตามบุคลิกของโฮชิโนะเเล้ว
it is not the end.
จะจบแบบนี้ได้ยังไง
She must be up to something.
เธอต้องมีอย่างอื่น
Right.
เออใช่ อันนี้
Today is your birthday!
วันนี้เป็นวันเกิดของคุณใช่มั้ย
This is for you.
ให้คุณ
Don't wear until you have made your decision.
อย่าไปจนกว่าคุณจะตอบ
At this point, it's time for you to provoke me!
มาถึงขนาดนี้เเล้ว คุณกำลังยั่วโมโหฉันเหรอ
Come, show your nature, Hoshino!
มา เปิดเผยตัวตนมาเถอะ โฮชิโนะ
Thank you. I'll cherish it.
ขอบคุณ ฉันจะรักษาให้ดีเลย
I lost. Hoshino
ฉันเเพ้เอง โฮชิโนะ
So it is
อย่างงี้นี่เอง
Aren't you a little disappointed.
แอบผิดหวังใช่มั้ยล่ะ
So noisy!
หนวกหูมาก
Anyway, how is this a proposal?
นี่มันเหมือนขอเเต่งงานตรงไหนเนี่ย
Because of your reaction.
ก็เพราะคุณปฏิกิริยาเเบบนั้น
A while after we encountered Kisei Chuu.
เวลาผ่านไปหลังจากที่เราเจอคิเซย์
I saw you wearing the hairpin.
ฉันเห็นคุณติดกิ๊บนั่น
I was going to ask you to leave school with me.
ฉันวางแผนที่จะชวนคุณกลับด้วยกันหลังเลิกเรียน
As a joke, please leave it on your strange surname.
ล้อเล่นหน่า คุณนี่แปลกเนอะ
How can it be...
แปลกยังไง…
At that time, I didn't know why I was suddenly hated by you.
ฉันไม่รู้ว่าทำไมจู่ๆถึงโดนคุณเกลียดเข้า
I see. You forgot.
อย่างงี้นี่เอง คุณลืมไปแล้วเหรอ
It dose not expect.
ไม่คิดว่า
The memory of the gift disappeared with Kisei Chuu.
ความทรงจำของของขวัญจะหายไปพร้อมกับคิเซย์จู
Have I bought this hairpin?
ฉันเคยซื้อกิ๊บนี้มาด้วยเหรอ
Forget it.
ช่าวมันเถอะ
It's cute, just wear it!
ยังไงก็น่ารักดี ติดไปเถอะ
That means.
นั่นหมายความว่า
I have been,
ตอนนั้นมาจนุถึงตอนนี้
always interact with Enjo under the situation of accepting the engagement?
ยอมหมั้นมาโดยตลอด เคยกับเอนโจรึเปล่า
Like that time...
ตอนนั้นเหมือนจะแล้วตอนนั้นก็เหมือนจะ ...
I feel so humiliated and want to go away immediately.
ฉันรู้สึกอายมาก อยากจะหายตัวจริงๆ
Why are you so anxious?
ทำไมคุณถึงกังวลมาก
He has obviously seen the more embarrassing side before.
เขาเคยเห็นเเล้ว เเต่ลำบากใจกว่าเดิมอีก
It's your fault.
จริงๆเลย
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
ทำไมไม่บอกฉันก่อน
And after reading the letter, I immediately agreed.
และหลังจากอ่านจดหมายฉันก็ตอบตกลงทันที
I didn't know you are so innocent.
ไม่คิดว่าคุณก็ไร้เดียวสาเหมือนกันนะเนี่ย
The other side, I have become very good at talking back now.
อีกร่างของฉันตอนนี้ย้อนคำเก่งหนิ
What was that?
เมื่อกี้คืออะไร
Could it be Kisei Chuu?
อาจจะเป็นคิเซย์จู
No, I guess it's a cat or something.
ไม่ ฉันเดาว่ามันเป็นแมวหรืออะไร
Is there a cat type?
หรือว่าจะเป็นประเภทพวกแมวเหรอ
No. I'm not talking about Kisei Chuu.
ไม่ ฉันไม่ได้พูดถึงคิเซย์จูอยู่เหรอ
Civet cat! ?
เเมวเสือดาว!?
How could it appear in such place
มันมาปรากฏในสถานที่เช่นนี้ได้อย่างไร
No. It's a raccoon.
ไม่ ตัวนี้มันเป็นแรคคูน
It's so cute!
น่ารักจัง
Come here, good boy!
เด็กดีมาทางนี้เร็ว
It's dangerous.
มันอันตรายนะ
It ran away.
มันหนีไปแล้ว
I didn't see anything.
ไม่เห็นมีอะไรเลย
It's not like this.
ไม่ใช่แบบนี้ ไม่ใช่แบบนี้
I just said.
ฉันเพิ่งพูดไป
This is what Cong Yu forgot to take.
นี่คือของที่มุราซาเมะลืมพกไป
I plan to return it to her next time.
ฉันกะว่าจะคืนให้เธอในครั้งหน้า
If that's really the case.
ถ้าเป็นอย่างนั้นจริงๆ
Then you can just leave it to Ruocao?
งั้นคุณให้วากากุซะก็ได้หนิ
You're right.
เออใช่
But that's not bad.
แต่นี่ก็ไม่เลวนะ
This means Hoshino finally has the consciousness of being a hero.
นั่นหมายความว่าโฮชิโนะก็มีลางที่จะเป็นฮีโร่เเล้วสิ
Don't draw conclusions.
อย่าอ้างสิทธิ์และหาข้อสรุปเร็ว
I'm just joking.
ฉันล้อเล่นหน่า
You're so serious now...
ตอนนี้คุณจริงจังขนาดนี้จะ ...
So I told you,
ฉันพูดทั้งหมดเเล้วไม่ใช่เหรอ
take it!
เอาไป
I borrow you the coat, take it and put it on.
เอาเสื้อโค้ทไปใส่ซะ
As if she goes away.
ดูเหมือนเธอจะไปแล้ว
Sorry to push you down.
ขอโทษที่ผลักคุณ
No. Thanks to that. I was finally saved.
ไม่ ต้องขอบคุณที่ทำให้รอดมาได้
Even though it was a desperate move,
แม้ว่าจะเป็นการรีบร้อนก็ตาม
I would have done it of my own accord.
แต่ไม่คิดว่าฉันจะทำมันด้วยตัวเองได้ด้วย
After hearing what Enjo just said
ฉันได้ยินเยนโจพูดเมื่อกี้
Am I swayed?
หวั่นไหวหรือเปล่า
Since being attacked by Kisei Chuu,
เนื่องจากถูกคิเซย์จูโจมตี
I do not want to experience the feeling of humiliation,
ฉันไม่อยากจะสัมผัสกับความรู้สึกที่น่าอับอายนั้นอีก
so I choose to stay away from guys.
นั่นคือเหตุผลที่ฉันเลือกที่จะอยู่ห่างจากผู้ชาย
Isn't it the same as before?
แบบนี้ก็กลับไปเป็นเหมือนเมื่อก่อนเเล้วไม่ใช่เหรอ
But if,
แต่ถ้าพูดว่า
I didn't meet Kisei Chuu.
ถ้าฉันไม่เจอคิเซย์จู
Right.
เออใช่
As you just said,
อย่างที่บอก
I don't seem to give you a clear answer yet.
ฉันยังไม่ได้ให้คำตอบที่ชัดเจนกับคุณเลยใช่มั้ย
No, after all, I was just young at that time.
ไม่เลยฉันยังเด็กและมีพลัง
Let it go！
ลืมมันไปเถอะ
But like this。
แต่ว่า
Am I just like a useless person who can't even answer a confession?
เเค่คำตอบฉันยังให้ไม่ได้ฉันนี่มันใช้ไม่ได้ขนาดนั้นเลยเหรอ
Is that right?
เหรอ
So what if.
ดังนั้นถ้า
Our relationship can be restored to what it was before we met Kisei Chuu.
ถ้าความสัมพันธ์ของเราสามารถกลับคืนสู่สภาพเดิมจนถึงวันที่เจอคิเซย์จู
If we can successfully wipe out all Kisei Chuus,
หากเรากำจัดคิเซย์จูทั้งหมดได้สำเร็จ
I will answer you at that time.
ฉันจะให้คำตอบคุณ
But,
แต่
if you dare to change your mind to others.
ถ้าคุณกล้าเปลี่ยนใจก่อน
I will not forgive you.
ฉันจะไม่ไว้คุณ
What is the situation?
นี่เกิดเรื่องอะไร
Could it be that...
เป็นไปได้มั้ย ... ที่ ...
Slowly, I need to calm down.
ช้าๆหน่อย ฉันสงบสติ
It can't be happening.
ไม่มีทางที่จะเป็นอย่างงั้น
Anyway,
อย่างไรก็ตาม
I need to contact Uncle first.
คุณต้องติดต่อคุณลุงก่อน
The number you dailed cannot be connected.
การโทรที่คุณโทรไม่สามารถใช้งานได้ในขณะนี้
Uncle's cell phone is out of charge.
แบตโทรศัพท์ของลุงเหมือนจะหมด
What shall I do?
จะทำยังไงดี
There's no solution.
ไม่มีทางอื่นเเล้ว
Like this time,
เหมือนครั้งนี้
as a man, you needs to know how to guide each other.
เป็นผู้ชายต้องรู้วิธีการเป็นผู้นำนะ
Let's go back by taxi.
พวกเราเรียกแท็กซี่กลับกันเถอะ
SUPER HXEROS
ซุปเปอร์HXEROS
Next Words "Goodbye HXEROS"
ตอนต่อไป"ลาก่อน HXEROS "